{
  "Items": [
    {
        "question": "Find the odd number",
        "answers": [
            "22",
            "33",
            "88",
            "66"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "33"
    },

    {
      "question": "Find the even number",
      "answers": [
        "22",
        "77",
        "11",
        "33"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "22"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 8 X 8 ?",
        "answers": [
            "64",
            "74",
            "84",
            "88"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "64"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 7 X 3 ?",
        "answers": [
            "73",
            "21",
            "10",
            "37"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "21"
    },


    {
        "question": "Find the even number",
        "answers": [
            "11",
            "12",
            "13",
            "15"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "12"
    },

    {
        "question": "Find the even number",
        "answers": [
            "85",
            "87",
            "89",
            "90"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "90"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 6 X 8 ?",
        "answers": [
            "68",
            "14",
            "48",
            "33"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "48"
    },

    {
        "question": "Find the odd number",
        "answers": [
            "30",
            "31",
            "32",
            "36"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "31"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 4 X 6 ?",
        "answers": [
            "10",
            "24",
            "46",
            "18"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "24"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is 5 X 5 ?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "55",
            "15",
            "25"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "25"
    }
  ]
}